virginnigeria.com 2014-12-23

# Privacy Policy - Virgin.com

If you would like to go straight to our cookie information, click here.

Here at Virgin.com Limited ("Virgin.com", "we" or "us"), we take your privacy seriously. We're committed to protecting the privacy of any personal information you give us. We will comply with the UK's Data Protection Act 1998 and related UK legislation. We are registered on the public register of data controllers maintained by the Information Commissioner in the UK.

We have a philosophy here about the way we use your consent to be contacted (if you give us that consent). If you hear from us, we will always aim to be respectful, relevant and appropriate. If at any time you don't feel we've lived up to our philosophy, please let us know straight away by getting in touch with us.

Please take the time to read this privacy policy, which is part of our terms of use. By using the Virgin.com site, including signing up for our newsletter, you are agreeing to be bound by the Terms and Conditions including this privacy policy. This policy explains how we collect, use and store the personal information you provide to us. 'Personal information' is information which identifies you or another person, or is capable of doing so.

This policy may change from time to time and, if it does, the up-to-date version will always be available on the Virgin.com site. Please note that by continuing to use the Virgin.com site you are agreeing to any updated versions.

## What are cookies?

We use "cookies" to store and collect information regarding your use of our site. Cookies are small pieces of information stored by the browser on your computer's hard drive. They send the information stored on them back to our web server when you access our site. These cookies enable us to load the site in such a way as to reflect your personal preferences (based on your previous browsing on Virgin.com as well as keywords we may be able to gather from the URLs of webpages from which you accessed Virgin.com, your IP address and any search engine used to reach Virgin.com). We use these cookies to improve your experience on our site and recommend content that may be of interest to you. You can find out more about cookies at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and more about the cookies we use below.

## What cookies do we use?

We only set a few cookies ourselves, but when we include content from other sites (like Facebook or Twitter), they also get the opportunity to set cookies, to help them serve their content better. We've broken down the main uses of cookies you'll see on the site below, and what they are used for, but we can't guarantee that we'll have listed every cookie you might get from a third party - they can change them at any time as their needs change.

## The Virgin cookie:

\- Contains a random ID

\- This id is then used to store information about your browsing history on Virgin.com

\- Uses an encrypted section of the cookie to ensure that no other user can "simulate" your cookie and impersonate you

\- Has an expiry of 30 days

For more information please get in touch with the webmaster at the address below:

The Webmaster  
Virgin.com Limited  
c/o Virgin Management Limited  
The Battleship Building  
179 Harrow Road  
London W2 6NB  
UK

## Cookies for Measuring Web Traffic

We make use of a tool from Google called Google analytics which tells us about the way people are using Virgin.com. It uses cookies to detect that someone has been to the site before, so that we can see how often people return to the site, how long they stay, and where on Virgin.com they tend to go. We use this to try to work out what kind of experience they're having on the site, so we can make it better.

Google Analytics sets cookies to help us accurately estimate the number of people visiting Virgin.com, and let us see how they're moving around the site. We use this when we make decisions on the type of content we create and how we structure the site. [To read Google’s privacy policy please click here. ](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en_uk/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

## Cookies From Social Networks

Because Virgin (and Richard) have a strong presence on various social networks, we try and make it as easy as possible to share content and to see what content is popular on those networks. For that reason we include recommendations from Facebook, tweets from Twitter, content from Google+ and add buttons to allow people to easily share to those networks. We also use Facebook to power the commenting functionality on the site.

When we include these social 'plugins', it gives those sites the flexibility to use cookies. They can't read any cookies we set from Virgin.com, and we can't read any cookies they set, but it lets them do the same kind of traffic measuring that we do on the rest of Virgin.com, and it also lets them know whether you're logged in. For example, if you're logged in to Facebook, read a post by Richard Branson and want to make a comment, you can do that straight away without having to log in again - we never know whether you're logged in or not, as you communicate directly with Facebook, through their plugins on our site.

## Facebook

We use several Facebook social plugins on Virgin.com, including the Like button, Facebook comments, recommendations and connect. Facebook will access some cookies if you have been to Facebook previously. If you haven't visited Facebook, no cookies will be added. For more information about how Facebook uses cookies, please see their support site <http://www.facebook.com/help/445588775451827.>

## Twitter

We make use of Twitter social plugins in order to allow following our Twitter accounts easily, share content via Twitter, and to display the latest tweet for Virgin and Richard Branson. Twitter makes use of cookies to improve its own service. You can read more about how Twitter users cookies in their privacy policy  <https://twitter.com/privacy>

## Add this

We use ‘Add This’ on our site to enable you to easily share the content you view on Virgin.com. For more information about ’Add This’, see their privacy policy <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy#.UjdI8cakr6M>

## Google+

We include a Google+ plugin on many of our news and blog post pages to allow viewers to share links via that service. That plugin sets the following cookies, though you will get a different mix of cookies depending on whether you are logged in to Google and Google+, or not. For more information about the Google +1 button, see their privacy policy <http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/+/policy/+1button.html>

## Cookies For Adverts

We have a number of spots around the site that show advertisements for companies in the Virgin Group. These are managed through a system called Google Doubleclick For Publishers. We use this for the obvious things, like the banner advertisements, but also for purposes like the logos of the Featured Companies. Doubleclick make use of cookies in order to track who has sent what adverts, in order to track which adverts are working better.

## Google Doubleclick

One of the ways that we link to the different Virgin companies on Virgin.com is via advertising positions. These include banner ads, but also the logos of Featured Companies on the front page. This allows us to track which adverts are doing well, and it also makes it easy for companies in the Virgin Group to give us assets to put in those slots. We use a platform called Doubleclick for Publishers, which is part of Google's advertising system. For more information about Doubleclick, privacy, and opting out of ad tracking, see this Google page on ad privacy <http://www.google.co.uk/policies/technologies/ads/>

## Cookies for Content

We include content from other sites in our updates, most notably YouTube videos. When we do this, YouTube may store cookies in order to track how people are watching videos from their site.

## How do we collect information from you with Facebook Connect?

When you use Virgin.com, you have the option to connect your Facebook account to Virgin.com. If you decide to ‘connect’ your Facebook account, we will gather certain information from your account so that we can display the content on the site in a way that we think would be optimal for your enjoyment of the site.

In order for us to access this information, you will have to manually click the Facebook Connect button on the site. This will trigger a pop-up window from Facebook directly, asking for permission for us to access the data with checkboxes in this pop-up for your Facebook ‘likes’ and ‘Check-ins’.

## What information do we collect when you use Facebook Connect?

We collect information on your likes that are included on your Facebook page to try and improve the content on the site. If you choose to connect but do not tick the boxes, we may still have access to your basic information posted on Facebook but not your likes an interests. Rest assured that we do not store your email address, Facebook username or your user ID or any other information from your Facebook profile that could identify you directly.

## What information do we collect if you sign up for our newsletter?

If you want to sign up to receive our newsletter we will collect the following personal information from you: your email address, name, date of birth and what you are interested in hearing more about. 

## Will we use your information for marketing?

We may display offers, promotions, products or services on the site which we think will interest you based upon the  information we collect from your cookies and from Facebook Connect.

## How else will we use your information?

We may also use your information for the following purposes:

To help provide services to you

To send you our newsletter if you have signed up to receive it.  
To carry out surveys occasionally and to analyse our user base — ultimately we want to ensure that [www.virgin.com ](http://www.virgin.com/)provides everything that you — our audience — is looking for  
To check whether you are eligible for a competition and to contact you if you win  
To comply with the law  
As we feel is necessary to prevent illegal activity or to protect our interests

And we won't keep hold of your personal information for longer than is reasonably necessary or required by law.

## Will we share your information with anyone else?

Only if…

You specifically request this, such as when you submit information to enquire about jobs or submit a job application through [www.virgin.com](http://www.virgin.com/)  
We are required to do so to comply with the law or with the directions of the courts or other authorities  
We feel it is reasonably necessary to prevent illegal activity or to protect our interests  
Other Virgin companies products and services may interest you  
It helps our trusted third party service providers to provide and improve our service to you or to carry out surveys and user analysis to understand your needs and preferences. We will also share your information with MailChimp, who securely host emails and act as a supplier to distribute our newsletter. We require these service providers to keep your personal information safe and secure. These trusted third parties would only be permitted to use your personal information for the purposes we specify.

We may share some broader statistics and customer profiling information with third parties and other Virgin companies - but we'll keep it anonymous, so you won't be identifiable from that data.

We won't rent or sell our user's details to any other organisation or individual.

## What if you post information on our site?

This site contains an opportunity for users to comment on content on the site ("User Content"). It is information in the public domain, so it may be accessed by any person using the web in any part of the world and can be found using independent search engines. So, if you choose to post information to the interactive parts of our site, we have to state that you do so at your own risk. This is the case whether the User Content is uploaded directly onto[ www.virgin.com](http://www.virgin.com/) or through a connected site.

This means your User Content:

Won't have its usage and circulation limited as described in the sections of this policy above headed 'Will we use your information for marketing?', 'How else will we use your information?' and 'Will we share your information with anyone else?'  
Won't be protected as described in the section of this policy below headed 'Will we be transferring any personal information outside the EU?'  
Won't be held securely as described in the section of this policy below headed 'Keeping your information safe'

We are obliged by our legal eagles to state that neither Virgin.com nor any other Virgin company will be liable to you or to any third party for any loss or damage resulting from any User Content posted on the Virgin.com site.

However, if you upload User Content to our site using the Facebook Connect function, we will protect your privacy consistently with your Facebook privacy settings.

Please read our Terms and Conditions for more information about posting User Content. If you register on the site, you'll need to comply with our [Terms and Conditions.](http://www.virgin.com/terms)

## To read more about our cookie policy click here.

If you have any concerns about User Content appearing on this site, please Contact Us.

## How will we make sure our site is secure?

We follow strict security procedures as to how your personal information is stored and used, and who sees it, to help stop any unauthorised person getting hold of it. All personal information you register on this site will be located behind a firewall. We take security extremely seriously but as no system is 100% secure, we can't completely guarantee the protection of your personal information, any more than any other organisation can. So we can't accept any liability for the loss, theft or misuse of the personal information which you've registered on this website if there is a security breach. If you submit a business proposal to us, your business proposal information will be held subject to the terms and conditions of the Business Proposal Submission Agreement.

## Will we be transferring any personal information outside the EU?

Countries outside the European Union may have a lower standard of protection for personal information than that required by EU data protection laws. The information we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored, outside the EU (including for example in the United States) and may also be processed by people operating outside the EU who work for us or one of our suppliers. If we need to transfer your data to a company based outside the EU (e.g. if our hosting company is based in the US), we'll take steps to make sure your personal data is handled in line with EU law.

## What about personal information relating to minors?

Protecting the online privacy of children is especially important. If you are under 18 years old, please do not provide us with your name, contact details or any other information about yourself. To find out more, please read our  Terms and Conditions.

## Are you protected by this policy outside www.virgin.com?

Our site contains links to other websites. Obviously, we don't have any control over them and take no responsibility for any information you give them. Other sites have different privacy and security policies, which we advise you to read.

## How you can access your information

You can request, at any time, access to the personal information we hold about you. You can write to us at the following address requesting access to your personal information.

The Webmaster  
Virgin.com Limited  
c/o Virgin Management Limited  
The Battleship Building  
179 Harrow Road  
London W2 6NB  
UK

You are entitled to be told by us whether we or someone else on our behalf is processing your personal information; what personal information we hold; details of the purposes for the processing of your personal information; and details of any third party with whom your personal information has been shared. (We may charge a small admin fee for providing this information). You can also request that we correct any personal information which we hold about you where it is inaccurate.

Sometimes you may be asked to provide proof of identity before we show you your personal information - that's so we can prevent unauthorised access.

## Talk to us

If you have any queries, comments or complaints regarding this privacy policy, just get in touch. You can contact us through the Contact Us section of this site or write to us at the address set out above.

This policy was last updated on 10 July 2014.
